[{"id":711,"question":"Are arrays supported in shell scripts?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":"Yes but only under certain conditions","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"},{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":943,"question":"What does PVC stand for?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Pod Volume Claim","answer_b":"Persistent Volume Container","answer_c":"Persistent Volume Claim","answer_d":"Pod Volume Container","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":339,"question":"Which of the following are not Numeric column types?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"BIGINT","answer_b":"LARGEINT","answer_c":"SMALLINT","answer_d":"DOUBLE","answer_e":"DECIMAL","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":662,"question":"Which command can give first found difference between two file after comparing?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"diff","answer_b":"cmp","answer_c":"Common","answer_d":"stat","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":548,"question":"Which of the following is used to add multiple line comments in PHP ?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"\/\/","answer_b":"\/* *\/","answer_c":"{{ }}","answer_d":"{\/ \\}","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"}][{"id":711,"question":"Are arrays supported in shell scripts?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"True","answer_b":"False","answer_c":"Yes but only under certain conditions","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"},{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":943,"question":"What does PVC stand for?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Pod Volume Claim","answer_b":"Persistent Volume Container","answer_c":"Persistent Volume Claim","answer_d":"Pod Volume Container","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Docker"}],"category":"Docker","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":339,"question":"Which of the following are not Numeric column types?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"BIGINT","answer_b":"LARGEINT","answer_c":"SMALLINT","answer_d":"DOUBLE","answer_e":"DECIMAL","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":662,"question":"Which command can give first found difference between two file after comparing?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"diff","answer_b":"cmp","answer_c":"Common","answer_d":"stat","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":548,"question":"Which of the following is used to add multiple line comments in PHP ?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"\/\/","answer_b":"\/* *\/","answer_c":"{{ }}","answer_d":"{\/ \\}","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"}]